Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Lust and Lies=
=الشهوة والكذب=
Tell them to leave.
اطلب منهم أن يرحلوا.
We'll carry on.
سوف نستمر.
Qingwan.
تشينغوان.
From this day on,
من هذا اليوم فصاعدا،
Sucheng
سوشينغ
belongs to just the two of us.
تنتمي إلينا نحن الاثنين فقط.
Qingwan?
تشينغوان؟
To smoke out the spies you planted around me,
لأتخلص من الجواسيس الذين زرعتهم حولي،
I played along with this charade.
لقد لعبت مع هذه الخدعة.
Did you enjoy it?
هل استمتعت بها؟
=Episode 24=
=الحلقة 24=
Cheng is back.
تشنغ عاد.
He told me
لقد قال لي
Sheng Weilian tried to kill him.
لقد حاول شينغ ويليان قتله.
He caught Sheng Weilian
قبض على شنغ ويليان
betraying the Huofeng Gang.
خيانة عصابة Huofeng.
That means he planted men in the ranks back then
وهذا يعني أنه زرع رجالاً في صفوفه آنذاك
to murder Huo Jin.
لقتل هيو جين.
He used Huo Beishan to wipe out
لقد استخدم هوو بيشان للقضاء عليه
the Huofeng Gang,
عصابة هوفينج,
then lent me soldiers so I could take revenge
ثم أقرضوني جنودًا حتى أتمكن من الانتقام
and kill...
و قتل...
He must've known you were Huo Qingwan,
لا بد أنه كان يعلم أنك هيو تشينغوان،
so he set it all up
لذلك قام بإعداد كل شيء
to turn us into enemies.
لتحويلنا إلى أعداء.
He planned to use you to finish me off
لقد خطط لاستخدامك للقضاء علي
and the Gu family.
وعائلة جو.
One scheme after another.
مخطط تلو الآخر.
Sucheng would have
كان من الممكن أن يكون سوتشنغ
nothing but the Sheng family.
لا شيء سوى عائلة شنغ.
He has people planted deep within
لقد زرع الناس في أعماقه
the Huo Army.
جيش هوو.
I can't act with that in mind.
لا أستطيع التصرف مع وضع ذلك في الاعتبار.
Then, I need to stay close.
إذن، أحتاج إلى البقاء قريبًا.
I'll marry him.
سأتزوجه
After all your scheming,
بعد كل مؤامراتك،
I was just another piece on your board, wasn't I?
لقد كنت مجرد قطعة أخرى في لوحتك، أليس كذلك؟
You know,
أنت تعرف،
on the chessboard,
على رقعة الشطرنج،
there are the king
هناك الملك
and the queen.
والملكة.
The place I've always left for you
المكان الذي تركته لك دائمًا
is the queen's seat.
هو مقعد الملكة.
I just want us to win this game together.
أريد فقط أن نفوز بهذه المباراة معًا.
Why won't you choose me?
لماذا لا تختارني؟
The queen?
الملكة؟
Isn't she the piece
أليست هي القطعة؟
that can be sacrificed for the king at any moment?
والتي يمكن التضحية بها من أجل الملك في أي لحظة؟
But Huo Xiu is not like you.
لكن هيو شيو ليس مثلك.
That's exactly why I chose him.
وهذا هو السبب بالضبط الذي جعلني أختاره.
All right.
حسنًا.
Fine.
بخير.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
for the sake of this game...
من أجل هذه اللعبة...
I had to sacrifice so many people.
لقد اضطررت للتضحية بالعديد من الناس.
Huo Jin.
هوو جين.
Mr. Ruan.
السيد روان.
Zhao Xun.
تشاو شون.
Madam Huo.
سيدتي هوو.
The Huofeng Gang.
عصابة هوفينج.
The Huo Army.
جيش هوو.
I've lost count at this point!
لقد فقدت العد في هذه المرحلة!
Zhao Xun and my mother...
تشاو شون وأمي...
Remember the earrings?
هل تتذكر الأقراط؟
That was my idea.
كانت هذه فكرتي.
That fool Zhao Xun.
هذا الأحمق تشاو شون.
I only said a few words to instigate him,
لقد قلت فقط بضع كلمات لتحريضه،
and he actually went to Huo Xiu
وذهب بالفعل إلى هوو شيو
and died for you.
ومات من أجلك.
And don't forget your useless mother.
ولا تنسى أمك عديمة الفائدة.
I had someone slip her poison.
لقد وضع أحدهم السم لها.
And she actually drank it.
وشربته بالفعل.
Hate me.
اكرهني.
Hate me all you want.
أكرهني كل ما تريد.
Then, you'll never forget me.
حينها لن تنساني أبدًا.
Want to kill me?
هل تريد قتلي؟
The Shengs won't let it slide.
لن يسمح الشنج بهذا الأمر.
Then, I'll wipe out the Sheng family.
ثم سأقوم بالقضاء على عائلة شينغ.
Kill him.
اقتله
I am the only one
انا الوحيد
who will ever love you.
من سيحبك إلى الأبد
Weilian.
ويليان.
If we can't be husband and wife in life,
إذا لم نستطع أن نكون زوجًا وزوجة في الحياة،
then let's be lovers in death.
إذن فلنكن عشاقًا في الموت.
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪
What went wrong?
ماذا حدث خطأ؟
For the sake of revenge,
من أجل الانتقام،
so many innocent people have died.
لقد مات الكثير من الأبرياء.
All of this...
كل هذا...
is beyond right or wrong.
هو أبعد من الصواب أو الخطأ.
We're victims
نحن ضحايا
and the perpetrators.
والجناة.
I once promised the First Madam
لقد وعدت السيدة الأولى ذات مرة
I would protect you for life.
سأحميك مدى الحياة.
I think
أظن
what she wanted most is for you to live.
ما كانت تريده أكثر من أي شيء آخر هو أن تعيش.
I've been living down in the cabin,
لقد كنت أعيش في الكابينة،
consumed by this hunger for revenge.
مستهلكة بهذا الجوع للانتقام.
Huo Xiu.
هوه شيوى.
I'm going out to see the world.
سأخرج لرؤية العالم.
All right.
حسنًا.
We'll leave Sucheng together.
سنترك سوتشنغ معًا.
You still have those men who follow you.
لا زال لديك هؤلاء الرجال الذين يتبعونك.
They stayed with you in Sucheng for 15 years
لقد مكثوا معك في سوتشنغ لمدة 15 عامًا
for the Gu family's revenge.
للانتقام لعائلة جو.
You can't abandon them.
لا يمكنك التخلي عنهم.
And the people of Sucheng
وشعب سوتشنغ
still need you to protect them.
ما زالوا بحاجة إليك لحمايتهم.
I carry too much blood and too many lost souls.
أحمل الكثير من الدماء والكثير من الأرواح الضائعة.
I want to go where I'm needed and atone.
أريد أن أذهب إلى حيث أحتاج وأكفر.
I wish you
أتمنى لك
a bright future in Sucheng.
مستقبل مشرق في سوتشنغ.
♪Amidst the light and shadow♪
♪وسط الضوء والظل♪
♪Love and hate blur together♪
♪الحب والكراهية يختلطان معًا♪
♪Why let ourselves fall deeper than we already are?♪
♪لماذا نسمح لأنفسنا بالسقوط بشكل أعمق مما نحن عليه بالفعل؟♪
♪Time can't outlast a heart that remembers♪
♪الوقت لا يمكن أن يدوم أكثر من القلب الذي يتذكر♪
What if...
ماذا إذا...
If we ever meet again...
إذا التقينا مرة أخرى...
Can we forgo the past?
هل يمكننا أن نتخلى عن الماضي؟
Only if
فقط إذا
I could atone for all my sins.
أستطيع أن أكفر عن كل خطاياي.
Easy, easy.
سهل، سهل.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Got it.
فهمتها.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Mr. Gu.
السيد جو.
With your donation,
مع تبرعك،
the people in the disaster area will get through this.
سوف يتمكن الناس في منطقة الكارثة من تجاوز هذا الأمر.
If you need anything,
إذا كنت بحاجة إلى أي شيء،
just let me know.
فقط دعني أعرف.
You've always been so charitable.
لقد كنت دائما خيريًا.
You must have helped a lot of people.
لا بد أنك ساعدت الكثير من الناس.
All for good karma, right?
كل هذا من أجل الخير، أليس كذلك؟
When you give to charity,
عندما تتبرع للأعمال الخيرية،
what do you pray for?
ماذا تصلي من أجله؟
My wife?
زوجتي؟
All she does is pray and light incense every day.
كل ما تفعله هو الصلاة وإشعال البخور كل يوم.
She always says
هي تقول دائما
that if you want something,
إذا كنت تريد شيئا،
you have to do more good deeds and build up good karma.
عليك أن تفعل المزيد من الأعمال الصالحة وتبني الكارما الجيدة.
But Mr. Gu,
ولكن السيد جو،
you have everything.
لديك كل شيء.
If there's something you want,
إذا كان هناك شيء تريده،
you can get it in a heartbeat.
يمكنك الحصول عليه في لمح البصر.
Yet, there are things beyond my reach.
ولكن هناك أشياء خارجة عن متناولي.
Dr. Huo,
الدكتور هوو
are you really going to the front?
هل انت حقا ذاهب الى الامام؟
They need me there.
إنهم يحتاجونني هناك.
I have to go.
يجب على  أن أذهب.
But it's dangerous out there.
لكن الأمر خطير هناك.
Even if it costs me my life,
حتى لو كلفني ذلك حياتي،
I'll must save the people.
لا بد لي من إنقاذ الناس.
No.
لا.
You have to stay alive.
يتوجب عليك البقاء على قيد الحياة.
There is someone you still want to see, right?
هل هناك شخص ما زال تريد رؤيته، أليس كذلك؟
Maybe
ربما
we're not meant to be.
نحن لسنا من المفترض أن نكون كذلك.
♪Listen, the bell rings from afar♪
♪استمع، الجرس يرن من بعيد♪
♪The fog lifts, your image still hazy♪
♪يرتفع الضباب، وصورتك لا تزال ضبابية♪
♪Do you remember the sound of the flute in the wind?♪
♪هل تتذكر صوت الناي في الريح؟♪
♪It whispers of the flame we shared♪
♪همس من اللهب الذي شاركناه♪
♪Having seen those prophecies left behind♪
♪بعد أن رأيت تلك النبوءات التي تركوها وراءهم♪
♪A sudden will to survive arises♪
♪تنشأ فجأة رغبة في البقاء♪
♪The ruan resounds with grandeur♪
♪الروان يتردد صداه بالعظمة♪
♪Under the pelting plum rain♪
♪تحت المطر الغزير من البرقوق♪
♪Everyone sings the final act♪
♪الجميع يغني الفصل الأخير♪
♪All fading away♪
♪كل شيء يتلاشى♪
♪The curtain falls♪
♪الستار يسقط♪